Let's walk through four hypothetical examples
下面举四个假设性例子
and assume that skewness is a reversal factor,
并假设偏态是逆转因子
which is another word for mean reversion.
它是均值回归的另一种说法
We'll be more specific and say that
具体而言
the maximum daily return over the trailing month is our measure of skew.
我们将用最后一个月的最大每日收益率衡量偏态
Let's also assume that the return over the trailing year is a momentum vector.
并且假设最后一年的收益率是动量向量
Notice that it's more precise to call
注意 更准确地说
our definition of skew as a measure of positive skew.
我们的偏态定义衡量的是正偏态
We aren't defining negative skew with a minimum over the trailing month.
我们没有定义负偏态 即最后一个月的最小值
Even though this is also a valid approach,
虽然这种方法也可行
for simplicity, we'll just be measuring positive skew.
但是为了简单起见 我们将衡量正偏态
Remember, the Alpha vector is a relative ranking exercise.
注意 Alpha 向量是一种相对排名操作
In our first scenario,
在第一种情形下
let's say momentum is positive and skew is positive.
假设动量为正 偏态也为正
This is the scenario that we saw in the introduction to this factor.
我们在此因子的介绍部分见到了这种情形
We can think of the positive skew as having
我们可以将正偏态看做
a dampening effect on the positive momentum of the stock.
对股票的正动量具有抑制效应
The paper calls this weakened momentum.
论文将其称为减弱动量
For our second scenario,
在第二种情形下
let's say momentum is still positive,
假设动量还是为正
but the skew is less positive.
但是偏态为正的幅度更小
The less positive skew may indicate that
幅度更小的偏态可能表示
future returns maybe stronger than if there were a positive skew.
未来收益率比正偏态更高
The paper calls this enhanced momentum.
论文将其称为增强动量
For our third scenario,
在第三种情形下
we'll look at negative momentum and positive skew.
动量为负 偏态为正
The paper describes this scenario by suggesting a phenomenon where investors are overly
论文将这种情形描述为
optimistic about a downward trending stock when the stock bounces backup temporarily.
股价暂时反弹 投资者对下降趋势过于乐观
The hypothesis continues to suggest that when the stock rebounds positively,
并且继续指出 当股票正面反弹时
individual investors may see this as a sign of recovery so they may buy as well.
散户可能会将其看做恢复信号 并买入股票
To conclude this scenario,
最后 在这种情形下
as fundamental still put downward pressure on the stock,
基本面依然对股票造成下降压力
the momentum then reasserts itself and the stock continues to slide downward.
动量再次体现出这种压力 并且股票继续下跌
This scenario is also referred to as enhanced momentum and is
这种情形也称为增强动量
the primary scenario for which the researchers
研究人员主要从这种情形中发现
found more significant effect of skewness on momentum.
偏态对动量具有更显著的影响
For our fourth scenario,
在第四种情形下
we'll look at negative momentum and less positive skew.
动量为负 偏态为正的幅度更小
The less positive skew has a dampening effect on the negative momentum,
幅度更小的偏态对负动量具有抑制效应
so it can be referred to as weakened momentum.
所以称为减弱动量
Now that you've seen how momentum and skew interact,
现在你已经知道动量和偏态的相互作用了
can you think of how these can be combined into a conditional factor?
你觉得应该如何将它们组合成条件因子？